That ICICI Lombard's share
fell by eight percent today, but in this very city,
mutual funds and foreign investors have
increased their holdings. Mutual funds
and foreign investors
understand the market better than us, so their Shirdi is
big. Today the share has fallen by eight percent.
What should I do? Let us understand this again.
[Music]
Hello, I am Praveen Sir, I welcome you to Mari Maharaj
channel. Today ICICI
Lombard's share fell by eight percent. You
think the results are so bad
that ICICI Lombard started its profit at
1.2 percent.
Compared to last year, the profit
is bigger by 1.2 percent. Such a small craft with this,
people sold inverters to others, that is why
its share fell by eight percent today and
sequential means the last doctor's
appointment
is subscribed. This
subscribed. But till the market closed today, it
showed a good recovery.
What should we do from here?
Before knowing what we have to do, we have to
understand whether it is nidhi or
not. Luvve Jain
works in general insurance and
you must have
heard that if you die, how will you recover?  You will get it so you will have to
die but what is general insurance,
you have
subscribed to your work
and
subscribe general insurance so this business
idea will
run from here that
providence will run and
because of the focus of appointment, now people have started
understanding it, so its growth is going to happen from
here onwards, these general insurance
businesses will grow big,
medical insurance and
property will do this and the
village will do it, so what do you
think is good for this business from here,
if you
definitely this business will remain and this business is
also going to be confirmed, the more it grows, the more it will
grow, hence property
is now the factory of school property, you
subscribe and
because of the code of medical insurance it has come into focus, people have started
understanding its importance and the company is fundamentally
very good and if you buy this company
around 1320, it is for long term,
service is for short term, so
where do we talk about long term,
you can do light business at 1320, if you
understand its business, so I have
said before also that if you do not understand the business, no matter
how good the company is, you can buy
it  You should not even touch it because the money
is yours, so until you do not understand
why it will start in the company,
why there will be a Bigg Boss in the company, you should
not touch it, I am not a cannon that if
my words cause the shares to fall or if there is any turmoil then
he does not want your money in it,
that is why you should use MS Word and if you feel
that the stock has potential then only buy it, but
never buy it in large quantity,
buy it in small quantities / then there are many or
so many shares that you will not be able to buy it, but
if the money gets stuck then what will you do, that is why if you want to
click on Bhaiya then subscribe, are you
angry